



































































Skip to main content
















.us









                   Deliver to
                

                   Vietnam
                






















All


Select the department you want to search in

All Departments
Arts & Crafts
Automotive
Baby
Beauty & Personal Care
Books
Boys' Fashion
Computers
Deals
Digital Music
Electronics
Girls' Fashion
Health & Household
Home & Kitchen
Industrial & Scientific
Kindle Store
Luggage
Men's Fashion
Movies & TV
Music, CDs & Vinyl
Pet Supplies
Prime Video
Software
Sports & Outdoors
Tools & Home Improvement
Toys & Games
Video Games
Women's Fashion






























EN





Hello, sign in
Account & Lists



Returns
& Orders



0






        Cart
        












All










Today's Deals
Customer Service
Registry
Gift Cards
Sell
Disability Customer Support





















































Amazon.com: Instant Pot Duo 7-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, Slow Cooker, Rice Cooker, Steamer, Sauté, Yogurt Maker, Warmer & Sterilizer, 8 Quart, Stainless Steel/Black & Silicone Lid, 8 quart, White: Home & Kitchen





























                Home & Kitchen
            


             ›
         


                Kitchen & Dining
            


             ›
         


                Small Appliances
            


             ›
         


                 Electric Pressure Cookers
             























 













 
 





















   



 $114.90$114.90  




 












   






  Delivery Tuesday, October 4. Order within 8 hrs 48 mins   

 

    


Deliver to Vietnam


    






  

 






      In Stock.            







     Qty: 1  2  3  Qty:1      






[{"displayPrice":"$114.90","priceAmount":114.90,"currencySymbol":"$","integerValue":"114","decimalSeparator":".","fractionalValue":"90","symbolPosition":"left","hasSpace":false,"showFractionalPartIfEmpty":true,"offerListingId":"1Szd2rRjxhbKQwkDQcV48DNJv6f9B8cB5kk%2BYltLPaznqJW7eS4h9n39VETXM5ntPk1lCku7PA6T0jjJJDuBq6UTwafagaKPjV0xUft2CA0U2o2ekalUc3xDvTMbYFLg8lObEgPQUDw9LOOn8wM0yWNfssjHFOHg","locale":"en-US","buyingOptionType":"BUNDLE"}]   $$114.90114.90  
                    ()
              Includes selected options.   Includes initial monthly payment and selected options.    
 Details  
       Price     ($114.90x)         $114.90          Subtotal    $$114.90114.90      Subtotal                  Initial payment breakdown           Shipping cost, delivery date, and order total (including tax) shown at checkout.
              



   Add to Cart   
 

        Buy Now    

   Enhancements you chose aren't available for this seller.    Details        To add the following enhancements to your purchase, choose a different seller.     %cardName%        ${cardName} not available for the seller you chose     ${cardName} unavailable for quantities greater than ${maxQuantity}.    

   
   Secure transaction     
  Your transaction is secure   We work hard to protect your security and privacy. Our payment security system encrypts your information during transmission. We don’t share your credit card details with third-party sellers, and we don’t sell your information to others. Learn more   
 

 


Ships from 



Amazon.com 



Sold by 



Amazon.com 


   Details        Ships from     Amazon.com        Sold by     Amazon.com        
 
  











































  









Add a gift receipt for easy returns 










 





  
   Add to List          Added to            Unable to add item to List. Please try again.                   Sorry, there was a problem.   There was an error retrieving your Wish Lists. Please try again.           Sorry, there was a problem.   List unavailable.         
  




   
 





            



  
   










 





    Have one to sell?      Sell on Amazon    




 






    



     



Image Unavailable  Image not available forColor: 
  





   
 
    
 
    
 
   To view this video download   Flash Player     

                                                                          
 
   

 
 



                    VIDEOS 



                    360° VIEW 



                    IMAGES 





 











































 
 






      







          Instant Pot Duo 7-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, Slow Cooker, Rice Cooker, Steamer, Sauté, Yogurt Maker, Warmer & Sterilizer, 8 Quart, Stainless Steel/Black & Silicone Lid, 8 quart, White           

 Visit the Instant Pot Store  



 
  4.7 out of 5 stars    
    12 ratings   




 






 









  Bundle List Price:  $134.94$134.94 
 
 Bundle Price: $114.90$114.90 










 

 





    You Save:    $20.04$20.04 (14%) 



    












 









  







 




















  
   









  Enhance your purchase            
 



            

 Product details    Brand   Instant Pot     Capacity   8 Quarts     Material   Stainless steel, Silicone     Control Method   Touch     Operation Mode   Automatic     Is Dishwasher Safe   Yes    
 

    
 This fits your .
     
  Make sure this fits by entering your model number. 
 
 Product 1: 7-IN-1 FUNCTIONALITY: Pressure cook, slow cook, rice cooker, yogurt maker, steamer, sauté pan and food warmer   Product 1: QUICK ONE-TOUCH COOKING: 13 customizable Smart Programs for pressure cooking ribs, soups, beans, rice, poultry, yogurt, desserts and more   Product 1: COOK FAST OR SLOW: Pressure cook delicious one-pot meals up to 70% faster than traditional cooking methods or slow cook your favorite traditional recipes – just like grandma used to make   Product 1: QUICK AND EASY CLEAN UP: Finger-print resistant, stainless-steel sides and dishwasher-safe lid, inner pot, and accessories   Product 2: Creates an airtight and watertight seal on the Instant Pot stainless steel inner pot   Product 2: Manufactured from the highest quality food safe silicone, passed FDA and LFGB tests for safety, including food safety   Product 2: Dishwasher safe   Product 2: Designed for Instant Pot 8 quart   
 See more product details    



 


  Customer ratings by feature         Easy to clean     5.0   5.0          Safety Features     5.0   5.0            Versatility     5.0   5.0        See all reviews      
 See more 
 
 



 




 



            













Note: Products with electrical plugs are designed for use in the US. Outlets and voltage differ internationally and this product may require an adapter or converter for use in your destination. Please check compatibility before purchasing.














  



















This bundle contains 2 items  (may ship separately) 
  
       
1 of Instant Pot Duo 7-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, Slow Cooker, Rice Cooker, Steamer, Sauté, Yogurt Maker, Warmer & Sterilizer, Includes App With Over 800 Recipes, Stainless Steel, 8 Quart 

 (149,391) 

$99.95 
 7-IN-1 FUNCTIONALITY: Pressure cook, slow cook, rice cooker, yogurt maker, steamer, sauté pan and food warmer. QUICK ONE-TOUCH COOKING: 13 customizable Smart Programs for pressure cooking ribs, soups, beans, rice, poultry, yogurt, desserts and more. COOK FAST OR SLOW: Pressure cook delicious one-pot meals up to 70% faster than traditional cooking methods or slow cook your favorite traditional recipes – just like grandma used to make. QUICK AND EASY CLEAN UP: Finger-print resistant, stainless-steel sides and dishwasher-safe lid, inner pot, and accessories. SAFETY FEATURES: Includes over 10 safety features, plus overheat protection and safe-locking lid PERFECT FOR LARGER FAMILIES: Cook for up to 8 people – perfect for larger families, or meal prepping and batch cooking for singles and smaller families VERSATILE INNER COOKING POT: We use food-grade stainless-steel, a tri-ply bottom for more even cooking and perfect for sautéing DISCOVER AMAZING RECIPES: Download our free Instant Pot app, so you can create quick new favorites and prepare delicious meals, available iOS and Android.           
1 of Instant Pot Silicone Lid, 8 quart, White 

 (4,719) 

$14.95 
 Creates an airtight and watertight seal on the Instant Pot stainless steel inner pot Manufactured from the highest quality food safe silicone, passed FDA and LFGB tests for safety, including food safety Dishwasher safe Designed for Instant Pot 8 quart May not be compatible with the liner of other brands of electric pressure cooker    
    






Buy it with+Total price:To see our price, add these items to your cart. Add both to Cart  Choose items to buy together. This item: Instant Pot Duo 7-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, Slow Cooker, Rice Cooker, Steamer, Sauté, Yogurt Maker, Warmer & Sterilizer, 8 Quart, Stainless Steel/Black & Silicone Lid, 8 quart, White$114.90In Stock.Ships from and sold by Amazon.com.Instant Pot Ceramic Inner Cooking Pot - 6 Quart$24.95In Stock.Ships from and sold by Amazon.com.








 

            Discover similar items 


  
 

 

  

 


     Review       

 
   
  & Up  
  
  & Up  
  
  & Up  
  
  & Up  
   
 

     Price       

 
   
<$25 
  
$25 - $50 
  
$50 - $100 
  
$100 - $200 
  
>$200 
   
 

     Color       

 
   
Multi 
  
Blue 
  
Orange 
  
Brown 
  
Clear 
  
Purple 
  
Yellow 
  
Beige 
  
Black 
  
Stainless Steel 
  
Gold 
  
Ivory 
  
Red 
  
Grey 
  
Silver 
  
Green 
  
Pink 
  
White 
   
 

     Capacity       

 
   
Up to 3.9 cups 
  
4-4.9 cups 
  
5-5.9 cups 
  
6-6.9 cups 
  
7-9.9 cups 
  
10-10.9 cups 
  
11 cups & above 
   
 

     Slow Cooker Capacity       

 
   
Under 4 Quarts 
  
4 Quarts 
  
5 Quarts 
  
6 Quarts 
  
7 Quarts & Up 
   
 

     Product Grade       

 
   
Commercial Grade 
   
 

     Power       

 
   
1500 to 1599 W 
  
Up to 1499 W 
  
1600 W & above 
   
 

     Heat Source       

 
   
Gas 
  
Electric 
  
Induction 
   
 

     Material       

 
   
Aluminum 
  
Borosilicate Glass 
  
Cast Iron 
  
Ceramic 
  
Plastic 
  
Stainless Steel 
   
 

     Fryer Material       

 
   
Stainless Steel 
  
Aluminum 
  
Plastic 
   
 

     Slow Cooker Type       

 
   
Manual 
  
Programmable 
   
 

     Brand       

 
   
Ninja 
  
Generic 
  
Cuisinart 
  
BELLA 
  
T-fal 
  
DASH 
  
YIYIBYUS 
  
Gdrasuya10 
  
LEIGE 
  
TBVECHI 
  
TFCFL 
  
DNYSYSJ 
  
ALDKitchen 
  
Elite Gourmet 
  
DYRABREST 
   
 

     Width       

 
   
Up to 7.9 in 
  
8 to 9.9 in 
  
10 to 11.9 in 
  
12 to 13.9 in 
  
14 in & above 
   
 

     Controls Type       

 
   
Knob 
  
Push Button 
  
Touch 
   
 

     Material Type Free       

 
   
PFOA Free 
  
BPA Free 
  
PTFE Free 
   
 

     Special Features       

 
   
Electric Stovetop Compatible 
  
Gas Stovetop Compatible 
  
Induction Stovetop Compatible 
  
Manual 
  
Programmable 
   
 

     Number of Heating Elements       

 
   
1 
  
2 
  
3 
  
4 
  
5 
  
6 
   
 

     Heating Element       

 
   
Coil 
  
Induction 
  
Open 
  
Radiant 
  
Sealed 
   
 

     Depth       

 
   
Up to 8.9 in 
  
9 to 10.9 in 
  
11 to 12.9 in 
  
13 to 14.9 in 
  
15 in & above 
   
 

     Recommended Uses For Product       

 
   
Bake 
  
Broil 
  
Defrost 
  
Dehydrate 
  
Reheat 
  
Roast 
  
Steam 
   
 

     Height       

 
   
Up to 10.9 in 
  
11 to 12.9 in 
  
13 to 14.9 in 
  
15 in & above 
   
 

     Item Shape       

 
   
Oblong 
  
Oval 
  
Rectangular 
  
Round 
  
Square 
   
   

 
Clear All 
 

 
  
 

         
No results available. Please adjust the filters and try again. 
   
 No more recommendations. Try adjusting your filters.  
 





 
  
   
  
         
 
    8    


 
 
$108$10890   

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 





Best Seller
 
  
   
  
         
 
    50336    


 
 
$199$19990 Price: $249.98 

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 






 
  
   
  
         
 
    43    


 
 
$121$12190   

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 






 
  
   
  
         
 
    2    


 
 
$171$17195   

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 






 
  
   
  
         
 
    9    


 
 
$145$14596   

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 






 
  
   
  
         
 
    30    


 
 
$209$20990   

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 






 
  
   
  
         
 
    2    


 
 
$174$17494   

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 






 
  
   
  
         
 
    2    


 
 
$182$18295 Price: $222.94 

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 






 
  
   
  
         
 
    56    


 
 
$132$13290 Price: $152.94 

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 






 
  
   
  
         
 
    69    


 
 
$105$10596   

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 






 
  
   
  
         
 
    46    


 
 
$124$12490   

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 






 
  
   
  
         
 
    3    


 
 
$178$17895 Price: $209.98 

 
  
 
  See more like this   
 


 
  Show more   
 



                Explore more from Instant Pot            Sponsored                           Hide feedback    Page 1 of 1Start overPage 1 of 1  Previous page of related Sponsored Products          Feedback           Instant Pot Duo Plus 9-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, Slow Cooker, Rice Cooker, Ste...     50,324        #1 Best Seller       $99.95                    Feedback           Instant Pot Duo Crisp 9-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker and Air Fryer Combo with Stai...     529        $149.99                    Feedback           Instant Vortex Plus 10-Quart Air Fryer, From the Makers of Instant Pot, 7-in-10 Fun...     32,769        $139.99          Save $5.00 with coupon                 Feedback           Instant Vortex Pro Air Fryer, 10 Quart, 9-in-1 Rotisserie and Convection Oven, From...     13,349                                  Limited time deal                           $139.95          List: $169.99 (18% off)               Feedback           Instant Vortex Plus 6-Quart Air Fryer Oven, From the Makers of Instant Pot with Odo...     1,307                                  Limited time deal                           $129.95          List: $169.99 (24% off)               Feedback           Instant Electric Round Dutch Oven, 6-Quart 1500W, From the Makers of Instant Pot, 5...           1,015        $179.95          Save $17.96 with coupon                 Feedback           Instant Solo Single Serve Coffee Maker, From the Makers of Instant Pot, K-Cup Pod C...     1,735                                  Limited time deal                           $77.95          List: $119.99 (35% off)               Feedback           Instant Vortex 5.7QT Air Fryer Oven Combo, From the Makers of Instant Pot, Customiz...     4,008        $119.00           Next page of related Sponsored Products     







Brands in this category on AmazonSponsored Shop Ninja® Foodi Pressure CookersShop SharkNinja - SharkPrepare healthy delicious meals, simply & quicklyShop Instant PotAccessories Made to Cook and ProtectShop LOTTELI KITCHENSilicone SpatulaShop BESTZMWK















 











 
From the manufacturer 



  


 

 About Us   Instant Brands is home to iconic brands, including Instant, Corelle, Pyrex, Corningware, Snapware and Chicago Cutlery. We’re passionate about delivering products that facilitate the joy we find in cooking and sharing food with family and friends. And we’re dedicated to bringing ever-better products and experiences to food-loving people everywhere.  



 Read more  
  







   Compare with similar items       
 
    This item  Instant Pot Duo 7-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, Slow Cooker, Rice Cooker, Steamer, Sauté, Yogurt Maker, Warmer & Sterilizer, 8 Quart, Stainless Steel/Black & Silicone Lid, 8 quart, White       
 
  Luby Electric Pressure Cooker 6 Qt,17 Smart Programmable,Slow Cooker Yogurt Maker Rice Cooker Saute Steamer Egg Cooker Sous Vide Warmer,Red (GT606)       
   
  Instant Pot Duo Plus 9-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, Slow Cooker, Rice Cooker, Steamer, Sauté, Yogurt Maker, Warmer & Sterilizer, Includes App With Over 800 Recipes, Stainless Steel, 8 Quart    

        #1 Best Seller  
     
   
  Instant Pot Ultra 80 Ultra 8 Qt 10-in-1 Multi- Use Programmable Pressure Cooker, Slow Cooker, Rice Cooker, Yogurt Maker, Cake Maker, Egg Cooker, Sauté, and more, Stainless Steel/Black       
 
  Instant Pot Duo 7-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, Sterilizer, Slow Cooker, Rice Cooker, Steamer, Saute, Yogurt Maker, and Warmer, 8 Quart, 14 One-Touch Programs & 8 Quart Glass Lid       
 
  Instant Pot Duo Plus 9-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, Warmer & Sterilizer,8 Quart Stainless Steel/Black & Tempered Glass Lid, Stainless Steel Rim, for 5 Qt/L or 6 Qt/L Models                Add to Cart            Add to Cart            Add to Cart            Add to Cart            Add to Cart            Add to Cart       Customer Rating     4.7 out of 5 stars  (12)       4.5 out of 5 stars  (459)       4.7 out of 5 stars  (50336)       4.7 out of 5 stars  (25423)       4.8 out of 5 stars  (43)         (0)       Price   $114.90$114.90   $81.99$81.99   $99.95$99.95   $159.99$159.99   $121.90$121.90   $115.96$115.96     Sold By   Amazon.com   Amazon.com   Amazon.com   Amazon.com   Amazon.com   Amazon.com     Material   Silicone, Stainless steel   Aluminum, Stainless steel, PP, foam   Stainless steel   Stainless steel   Stainless steel   Stainless steel     Size   8Qt   6QT   8QT   8-QT   8-QT   8QT               Compare with similar items    


   Product Description    
 Instant Pot Duo 7-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, Slow Cooker, Rice Cooker, Steamer, Sauté, Yogurt Maker, Warmer & Sterilizer, 8 Quart, Stainless Steel/BlackEasy to use, easy to clean, fast, versatile, and convenient, the Instant Pot® Duo™ is the one that started it all. It replaces 7 kitchen appliances: pressure cooker, slow cooker, rice cooker, steamer, sauté pan, yogurt maker & warmer. With 13 built-in smart programs, cook your favorite dishes with the press of a button. The tri-ply, stainless steel inner pot offers quick, even heating performance. Redefine cooking and enjoy quick and easy meals anywhere, any time. The Instant Pot Duo offers the quality, convenience and versatility you’ve come to expect from Instant – discover amazing.Instant Pot Silicone Lid, 8 quart, WhiteThe Instant Pot silicone cover may be used on the Instant Pot inner pot to create an airtight and water tight seal for storage in your refrigerator.   



  




 
 
                          Product information 
       ASIN   B0B497HTJ8    Customer Reviews  

 
  4.7 out of 5 stars    
    12 ratings   


 4.7 out of 5 stars     Best Sellers Rank    #309,424 in Kitchen & Dining (See Top 100 in Kitchen & Dining)  #150 in Electric Pressure Cookers       Date First Available   June 16, 2022          Warranty & Support      If you'd like a copy of the manufacturer's warranty for a product found on Amazon.com, you can contact the manufacturer directly or visit their website for more information. Manufacturer's warranties may not apply in all cases, depending on factors like the use of the product, where the product was purchased, or who you purchased the product from. Please review the warranty carefully, and contact the manufacturer if you have any questions.      Feedback       
 Would you like to  tell us about a lower price?
          












 

VideosPage 1 of 1Start OverPage 1 of 1Previous pageVideos for related products 2:37  Click to play video  WHAT YOU GET & REVIEW: Instant Pot Duo Plus 9-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker Hammer and HomeVideos for related products 5:20  Click to play video  Instant Pot 3Qt Duo Mini Real Cooking Demo -Oat Groats Nutmeg NotebookVideos for related products 0:36  Click to play video  Instant Pro Plus with Wifi Sizzle Instant Brands LLC - AppliancesVideos for related products 10:00  Click to play video  Instant Pot Pro Crisp (8Qt) & Duo Crisp (6Qt) Comparisons! Everyday EasyVideos for related products 1:54  Click to play video  Our Point of View on Instant Pot Duo Pressure Cookers What Tools InsideVideos for related products 0:22  Click to play video  How to use the Glass Lid Yedi HousewareVideos for related products 1:35  Click to play video  Our Point of View on the Instant Pot 6 Quart Pressure Cooker What Tools InsideVideos for related products 3:08  Click to play video  Instant Pod Instant Brands LLC - AppliancesVideos for related products 0:29  Click to play video  Instant Pot Duo Nova Instant Brands LLC - AppliancesVideos for related products 5:53  Click to play video  Instant Pot Models Explained - DUO vs Plus vs Crisp vs Pro Vacuum Wars RecommendationsNext pageUpload your video Customer Review: WHAT YOU GET & REVIEW: Instant Pot Duo Plus 9-in-1 Electric Pressure CookerSee full review Hammer and Home  Earns Commissions  Earns Commissions 












                Related products with free delivery on eligible orders            Sponsored                           Hide feedback    Page 1 of 1Start overPage 1 of 1  Previous page of related Sponsored Products          Feedback           Instant Pot Duo Plus 9-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, Slow Cooker, Rice Cooker, Ste...     50,324        #1 Best Seller       $99.95                    Feedback           Instant Vortex Plus 6-Quart Air Fryer Oven, From the Makers of Instant Pot with Odo...     1,307                                  Limited time deal                           $129.95          List: $169.99 (24% off)               Feedback           Instant Omni Plus 19 QT/18L Air Fryer Toaster Oven Combo, From the Makers of Instan...     32,769                                  Limited time deal                           $199.95          List: $219.00 (9% off)               Feedback           Instant Vortex Pro Air Fryer, 10 Quart, 9-in-1 Rotisserie and Convection Oven, From...     13,349                                  Limited time deal                           $139.95          List: $169.99 (18% off)               Feedback           Instant Solo Single Serve Coffee Maker, From the Makers of Instant Pot, K-Cup Pod C...     1,735        $79.95                    Feedback           Instant Pot Duo Crisp 9-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker and Air Fryer Combo with Stai...     529        $149.99                    Feedback           Instant Electric Round Dutch Oven, 6-Quart 1500W, From the Makers of Instant Pot, 5...           1,015        $179.95                    Feedback           Instant Vortex 5.7QT Air Fryer Oven Combo, From the Makers of Instant Pot, Customiz...     4,008        $119.00                    Feedback           Toshiba Digital Programmable Rice Cooker, Steamer & Warmer, 3 Cups Uncooked Rice wi...           645        $72.42                    Feedback           Proctor-Silex Simplicity 4-in-1 Electric Pressure Cooker, 3 Quart Multi-Function Wi...     24        $82.99           Next page of related Sponsored Products     























	
		
		
		
			Customer questions & answers
		
	


                See questions and answers
            











Customer reviews4.7 out of 5 stars4.7 out of 5
            12 global ratings






            5 star
          












            
              87%
            
          






          4 star
        

          0% (0%)
        








          
            0%
          
        






            3 star
          












            
              13%
            
          






          2 star
        

          0% (0%)
        








          
            0%
          
        





          1 star
        

          0% (0%)
        








          
            0%
          
        






                How customer reviews and ratings work
            


                    Customer Reviews, including Product Star Ratings help customers to learn more about the product and decide whether it is the right product for them.
                

                    To calculate the overall star rating and percentage breakdown by star, we don’t use a simple average. Instead, our system considers things like how recent a review is and if the reviewer bought the item on Amazon. It also analyzed reviews to verify trustworthiness.
                

                    Learn more how customers reviews work on Amazon
                













        Top reviews
      

        Most recent
      
Top reviews












  Top reviews from the United States


There was a problem filtering reviews right now. Please try again later.Monique Dilley5.0 out of 5 stars
LOVE IT !!
Reviewed in the United States on August 23, 2022Verified Purchase
If you have been thinking go of getting an Instapot do it !! It has made dinner so much easier on days we both work ! Love it !!
Read more


          Helpful


Report abuse
Nicholas Schulze5.0 out of 5 stars
GREAT COOKER FOR CHIEFS!
Reviewed in the United States on August 6, 2022Verified Purchase
my partner and I just split up and took the pressure cooker... SO I had to buy my own I love it that much
Read more


          Helpful


Report abuse
Marian Robinson5.0 out of 5 stars
Just the right size
Reviewed in the United States on August 2, 2022Verified Purchase
It is very nice but I have not used it yet
Read more


          Helpful


Report abuse
Mimi5.0 out of 5 stars
Easy to use . Cooks yummy  food in minutes .
Reviewed in the United States on August 4, 2022Verified Purchase
Love this Instant Pot . It’s my second larger . Easy to use , easy to clean , no mess , food done  in minutes. Came packaged safely . Delivered w/ care . Instructions followed . Drivers profesional & friendly  .
Read more


          Helpful


Report abuse
See all reviews








































































                    Your recently viewed items and featured recommendations      ›    View or edit your browsing history     After viewing product detail pages, look here to find an easy way to navigate back to pages you are interested in.         Your recently viewed items and featured recommendations      ›    View or edit your browsing history     After viewing product detail pages, look here to find an easy way to navigate back to pages you are interested in.        




    Back to top
  





Get to Know Us


Careers


Blog


About Amazon


Investor Relations


Amazon Devices


Amazon Science





Make Money with Us


Sell products on Amazon


Sell on Amazon Business


Sell apps on Amazon


Become an Affiliate


Advertise Your Products


Self-Publish with Us


Host an Amazon Hub


›See More Make Money with Us





Amazon Payment Products


Amazon Business Card


Shop with Points


Reload Your Balance


Amazon Currency Converter





Let Us Help You


Amazon and COVID-19


Your Account


Your Orders


Shipping Rates & Policies


Returns & Replacements


Manage Your Content and Devices


Amazon Assistant


Help

















EnglishChoose a language for shopping.



$USD - U.S. Dollar



United StatesChoose a country/region for shopping.






Amazon MusicStream millionsof songs
Amazon AdvertisingFind, attract, andengage customers
Amazon DriveCloud storagefrom Amazon
6pmScore dealson fashion brands
AbeBooksBooks, art& collectibles
ACX Audiobook PublishingMade Easy
AlexaActionable Analyticsfor the Web
 

Sell on AmazonStart a Selling Account
Amazon BusinessEverything ForYour Business
AmazonGlobalShip OrdersInternationally
Home ServicesExperienced ProsHappiness Guarantee
Amazon IgniteSell your originalDigital EducationalResources
Amazon Web ServicesScalable CloudComputing Services
AudibleListen to Books & OriginalAudio Performances
 

Book DepositoryBooks With FreeDelivery Worldwide
Box Office MojoFind MovieBox Office Data
ComiXologyThousands ofDigital Comics
DPReviewDigitalPhotography
FabricSewing, Quilting& Knitting
GoodreadsBook reviews& recommendations
IMDbMovies, TV& Celebrities
 

IMDbProGet Info EntertainmentProfessionals Need
Kindle Direct PublishingIndie Digital & Print PublishingMade Easy

Prime Video DirectVideo DistributionMade Easy
ShopbopDesignerFashion Brands
Woot!Deals and Shenanigans
ZapposShoes &Clothing
RingSmart HomeSecurity Systems

 

 

eero WiFiStream 4K Videoin Every Room
BlinkSmart Securityfor Every Home

Neighbors App  Real-Time Crime& Safety Alerts

Amazon Subscription BoxesTop subscription boxes – right to your door
PillPackPharmacy Simplified
 




Conditions of UsePrivacy NoticeInterest-Based Ads© 1996-2022, Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates




















